Guide to the Astor Family Papers 1719-1943 MS 25
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Property Documents: Leases, Deeds, Mortgages, Maps, 1758-1940
  - Subseries I.20: Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1896-1902
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1896 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1897 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1899 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1900 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1901-1902 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.21: Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1903-1909
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1903-1904 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1905 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1906-1907 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1907 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1908 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1909 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.22: Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1910-1916
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1910 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1911 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1912 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1913 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1914 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1915 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1916 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Subseries I.23: Adams-Baldwin Letters to Adams-Baldwin Cables, 1890-1919
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1917 (Offsite-box 23, Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Adams-Baldwin Letters, 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 23, Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Baldwin to Adams Letters, 1915-1919 (Offsite-box 23, Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Adams-Baldwin Cables, 1890-1897 (Offsite-box 23, Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Adams-Baldwin Cables, 1890-1897 (Offsite-box 23, Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Subseries I.24: Adams-Baldwin Cables to Journal Transcrips London Accounts, 1890-1909
    - Adams-Baldwin Cables, 1898-1909 (Offsite-box 24, Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Cable Codes, n.d. (Offsite-box 24, Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1890-1893 (Offsite-box 24, Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1894-1895 (Offsite-box 24, Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1895-1897 (Offsite-box 24, Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1897-1898 (Offsite-box 24, Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1899-1900 (Offsite-box 24, Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Subseries I.25: Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1900-1906
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1900 (Offsite-box 25, Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1901 (Offsite-box 25, Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1902 (Offsite-box 25, Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1903 (Offsite-box 25, Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1904-1905 (Offsite-box 25, Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1905-1906 (Offsite-box 25, Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.26: Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1906-1912
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1906 (Offsite-box 26, Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1907 (Offsite-box 26, Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1908 (Offsite-box 26, Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1909 (Offsite-box 26, Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1910-1911 (Offsite-box 26, Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1911-1912 (Offsite-box 26, Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.27: Journal Transcripts London Accounts to Balance Sheets, 1890-1917
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box 27, Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1914-1915 (Offsite-box 27, Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Journal Transcripts London Accounts, 1916-1917 (Offsite-box 27, Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Balance Sheets 1890-1893 (Offsite-box 27, Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Balance Sheets 1894-1895 (Offsite-box 27, Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Balance Sheets 1895-1896 (Offsite-box 27, Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.28: Balance Sheets, 1897-1906
    - Balance Sheets 1897-1898 (Offsite-box 28, Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Balance Sheets 1899-1900 (Offsite-box 28, Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Balance Sheets 1901-1902 (Offsite-box 28, Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Balance Sheets 1903-1904 (Offsite-box 28, Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Balance Sheets 1905-1906 (Offsite-box 28, Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Subseries I.29: Balance Sheets, 1907-1919
    - Balance Sheets 1907-1908 (Offsite-box 29, Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Balance Sheets 1909-1910 (Offsite-box 29, Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Balance Sheets 1910-1911 (Offsite-box 29, Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Balance Sheets 1912-1914 (Offsite-box 29, Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Balance Sheets 1915-1916 (Offsite-box 29, Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Balance Sheets 1917-1918 (Offsite-box 29, Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Balance Sheets 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 29, Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Subseries I.30: Rothschild Freres to Hottinguer & Co., 1890-1918
    - Rothschild Freres 1890-1894 (Offsite-box 30, Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Rothschild Freres 1894-1895 (Offsite-box 30, Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Rothschild Freres 1896-1899 (Offsite-box 30, Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Rothschild Freres 1900-1908 (Offsite-box 30, Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Rothschild Freres 1909-1918 (Offsite-box 30, Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Hottinguer & Co. 1892-1894 (Offsite-box 30, Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Hottinguer & Co., 1895-1897 (Offsite-box 30, Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Subseries I.31: Hottinguer & Co. to Profit & Loss, 1898-1917
    - Hottinguer & Co. 1898-1899 (Offsite-box 31, Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Hottinguer & Co. 1900-1901 (Offsite-box 31, Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Hottinguer & Co. 1902-1904 (Offsite-box 31, Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Hottinguer & Co. 1905-1906 (Offsite-box 31, Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Hottinguer & Co. 1907-1909 (Offsite-box 31, Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Profit & Loss 1890-1905 (Offsite-box 31, Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Profit & Loss 1905-1917 (Offsite-box 31, Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Subseries I.32: Astor Homes to Ogden vs. Astor, 1794-1986
    - Astor Homes 1851-1986 (Offsite-box 32, Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Astor Homes: Red Hook 1847-1866 (Offsite-box 32, Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Astor Homes: Red Hook 1794-1874 (Offsite-box 32, Box 32, Folder 3)
    - John Jacob Astor I 1848-1891 (Offsite-box 32, Box 32, Folder 4)
    - John Jacob Astor I 1820-1880 (Offsite-box 32, Box 32, Folder 5)
    - John Jacob Astor I 1870-1889 (Offsite-box 32, Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Ogden vs. Astor 1850-1854 (Offsite-box 32, Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Subseries I.33: Ogden vs. Astor to Sophia Astor, 1836-1882
    - Ogden vs. Astor 1850-1854 (Offsite-box 33, Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Ogden vs. Astor 1850-1854 (Offsite-box 33, Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Ogden vs. Astor 1850-1854 (Offsite-box 33, Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Ogden vs. Astor 1850-1854 (Offsite-box 33, Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Sophia Astor 1836-1882 (Offsite-box 33, Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Subseries I.34: Sophia Astor to Miscellaneous, 1864-1935
    - Sophia Astor 1864-1890 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Waldorf Foundation 1836-1867 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Waldorf Foundation 1836-1868 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Waldorf Foundation 1836-1868 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 4)
    - William Backhouse Astor Jr., 1853-1881 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 5)
    - William Waldorf Astor 1890-1923 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 6)
    - William Waldorf Astor, 1922-1924 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 7)
    - William Waldorf Astor, 1916-1930 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 8)
    - William Waldorf Astor, 1920-1931 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1890-1935 (Offsite-box 34, Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Subseries I.35: Oversize Documents, 1758-1840
    Arrangement
    Each folder is arranged alphabetically by street name if it falls within the city of New York, and by city/town name when it is outside of New York.
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases A-B, 1807-1834 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases B, 1803-1828 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases B, 1794-1832 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases B, 1802-1828 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases B-C, 1802-1831 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases C-D, 1790-1831 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases D-G, 1787-1840 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases G-H, 1800-1835 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases H, 1806-1826 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases H-K, 1810-1851 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases L, 1807-1834 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases M, 1801-1835 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases N-R, 1790-1826 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases S, 1806-1865 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases T-V, 1804-1824 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases W, 1794-1833 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases W-Miscellaneous, 1801-1838 (Box Oversize Small, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases A-B, 1784-1838 (Box Oversize Medium, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases B-D, 1790-1811 (Box Oversize Medium, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases D-G, 1771-1824 (Box Oversize Medium, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases G-M, 1719-1828 (Box Oversize Medium, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases M-P, 1794-1804 (Box Oversize Medium, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases R-T, 1790-1816 (Box Oversize Medium, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases V-W, 1790-1832 (Box Oversize Medium, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases B, 1768-1825 (Box Oversize Large, Folder Astor Family Papers)
    - [Y-Astor Family Papers] Deeds and Leases B-H, 1758-1816 (Box Oversize Large, Folder Astor Family Papers)
- Series II: Letterbooks, Daybooks, Rent Rolls, Journals, and Ledgers, 1807-1943
  This collection contains volumes from 1807-1943 belonging to the Astor family and associates. It includes daybooks, rent rolls, map books, letterbooks (business and personal), ledgers and journals.
  - Subseries II.1: Astor Family, 1807-1943
    - Abstract of Title, 1807-1880 (Offsite-box AF-1, Volume 1)
    - House and Land Book, 1832 (Offsite-box AF-6, Volume 2)
    - Family and Trust Ledger, 1833-1849 (Offsite-box AF-7, Volume 3)
    - Maps of New York Properties and Mortgage Agreements, 1843-1851 (Offsite-box AF-7, Volume 4)
    - Supreme Court Case: Ogden vs. Astor, 1850-1854 (Offsite-box AF-7, Volume 5)
    - Deed Book, 1851-1890 (Offsite-box AF-7, Volume 6)
    - Map Book, 1891-1892 (Offsite-box AF-7, Volume 7)
    - Map Book, 1891-1892 (Offsite-box AF-8, Volume 7)
    - Real Estate Assessment, 1898-1929 (Offsite-box AF-1, Volume 8)
    - Map Book, 1915-1935 (Offsite-box AF-3, Volume 9)
    - Business Accounts, 1926-1943 (Offsite-box AF-8, Volume 10)
  - Subseries II.2: John Jacob Astor I, 1826-1878
    - Rent Roll: Lessees and Tenants of John Jacob Astor I, from Nov. 1826-May 1831, 1826-1831 (Offsite-box AF-8, Volume 11)
    - Ledger-Trust for Mrs. Eliza Rumpff, 1826-1839 (Offsite-box AF-1, Volume 12)
    - Journal-Trust for Mrs. Eliza Rumpff, 1826-1839 (Offsite-box AF-1, Volume 13)
    - Executors Estate of John Jacob Astor I: Accounts, 1836-1875 (Offsite-box AF-1, Volume 14)
    - Map Book, 1836-1878 (Offsite-box AF-6, Volume 15)
    - Rent Roll: Lessees and Tenants of John Jacob Astor I, 1841-1848 (Offsite-box AF-8, Volume 16)
    - Minutes of the Executors, Estate of John Jacob Astor, 1848-1854 (Offsite-box AF-8, Volume 17)
    - Executors Estate of John Jacob Astor I: Accounts, 1849-1872 (Offsite-box AF-1, Volume 18)
    - Executors Estate of John Jacob Astor I: Accounts, 1849-1872 (Offsite-box AF-1, Volume 18-A)
    - Valuation of Real Estate, 1847 (Offsite-box AF-1, Volume 19)
    - Deed of Appointment, 1854 (Offsite-box AF-8, Volume 20)
  - Subseries II.3: Henry Astor Estate, 1833-1855
    - Journal and Ledger, Estate of Henry Astor 1833-1834 (Offsite-box AF-4, Volume 21)
    - Journal and Ledger, Estate of Henry Astor 1833-1847 (Offsite-box AF-8, Volume 22)
    - Journal and Ledger, Estate of Henry Astor 1847-1855 (Offsite-box AF-3, Volume 23)
  - Subseries II.4: William Backhouse Astor, 1840-1875
    - Business Letterbook 1848-1852 (Offsite-box AF-9, Volume 24)
    - Business Letterbook 1852-1855 (Offsite-box AF-9, Volume 25)
    - Business Letterbook 1852-1857 (Offsite-box AF-3, Volume 26)
    - Business Letterbook 1855-1858 (Offsite-box AF-9, Volume 27)
    - Business Letterbook 1858-1873 (Offsite-box AF-5, Volume 28)
    - Business Letterbook 1859-1864 (Offsite-box AF-10, Volume 29)
    - Business Letterbook 1863-1868 (Offsite-box AF-10, Volume 30)
    - Business Letterbook 1868-1872 (Offsite-box AF-11, Volume 31)
    - Daybook 1854-1857 (Offsite-box AF-11, Volume 32)
    - Daybook 1866-1869 (Offsite-box AF-2, Volume 33)
    - Daybook 1872-1875 (Offsite-box AF-2, Volume 34)
    - Daybook 1875 (Offsite-box AF-2, Volume 35)
    - Estate Journal 1850-1853 (Offsite-box AF-5, Volume 36)
    - Estate Journal 1854-1857 (Offsite-box AF-5, Volume 37)
    - Estate Journal 1857-1861 (Offsite-box AF-4, Volume 38)
    - Estate Journal 1863-1866 (Offsite-box AF-11, Volume 39)
    - Estate Journal 1864-1868 (Offsite-box AF-4, Volume 40)
    - Estate Journal 1869-1872 (Offsite-box AF-21, Volume 41)
    - Estate Journal 1872-1875 (Offsite-box AF-21, Volume 42)
    - Memo Book, 1840-1843(?) (Offsite-box AF-20, Volume 43)
    - Mortgage Receipt Book, 1851-1859 (Offsite-box AF-10, Volume 44)
    - Valuation of Homes and Lands, 1847 (Offsite-box AF-20, Volume 45)
    - Valuation of Homes and Lands, 1847 (Offsite-box AF-12, Volume 45-A)
  - Subseries II.5: John Jacob Astor III, 1875-1913
    - Business Letterbook 1873-1891 (Offsite-box AF-22, Volume 46)
    - Business Letterbook 1875-1885 (Offsite-box AF-12, Volume 47)
    - Business Letterbook 1875-1890 (Offsite-box AF-13, Volume 48)
    - Business Letterbook 1885-1890 (Offsite-box AF-13, Volume 49)
    - Daybook, 1887-1890 (Offsite-box AF-14, Volume 50)
    - Tickler, 1890-1913 (Offsite-box AF-24, Volume 51)
  - Subseries II.6: William Waldorf Astor, 1890-1917
    - Expense Daybook 1895-1897 (Offsite-box AF-18, Volume 52)
    - Expense Daybook 1897-1900 (Offsite-box AF-18, Volume 53)
    - Expense Daybook 1900-1902 (Offsite-box AF-17, Volume 54)
    - Expense Daybook 1902-1905 (Offsite-box AF-17, Volume 55)
    - Expense Daybook 1905-1908 (Offsite-box AF-17, Volume 56)
    - Expense Daybook 1911-1913 (Offsite-box AF-17, Volume 57)
    - Expense Daybook 1913-1916 (Offsite-box AF-18, Volume 58)
    - Repair Orders, 1912-1917 (Offsite-box AF-25, Volume 59)
    - References 1890-1897 (Offsite-box AF-15, Volume 60)
    - References 1898-1902 (Offsite-box AF-19, Volume 61)
    - Rent Roll 1890-1895 (Offsite-box AF-26, Volume 62)
    - Rent Roll 1895-1898 (Offsite-box AF-27, Volume 63)
    - Rents Collected 1900-1902 (Offsite-box AF-22, Volume 64)
    - Rents Collected 1904-1906 (Offsite-box AF-22, Volume 65)
    - Rents Collected 1908-1909 (Offsite-box AF-23, Volume 66)
    - Rents Collected 1909-1911 (Offsite-box AF-23, Volume 67)
    - Rents Collected 1911-1913 (Offsite-box AF-24, Volume 68)
    - Rents Collected 1915-1918 (Offsite-box AF-30, Volume 68-A)
    - Rents Collected 1918-1919, 1818-1819 (Offsite-box AF-30, Volume 69)
  - Subseries II.7: C.W. Baldwin, 1880-1919
    - Business Letterbook 1880-1888 (Offsite-box AF-14, Volume 70)
    - Business Letterbook 1890-1903 (Offsite-box AF-16, Volume 71)
    - Business Letterbook 1893-1899 (Offsite-box AF-16, Volume 71-A)
    - Business Letterbook 1894-1895 (Offsite-box AF-16, Volume 72)
    - Business Letterbook 1895-1896 (Offsite-box AF-16, Volume 73)
    - Business Letterbook 1896-1898 (Offsite-box AF-16, Volume 74)
    - Business Letterbook 1901-1902 (Offsite-box AF-18, Volume 75)
    - Business Letterbook 1901-1909 (Offsite-box AF-19, Volume 76)
    - Business Letterbook 1902-1904 (Offsite-box AF-19, Volume 77)
    - Business Letterbook 1904-1906 (Offsite-box AF-19, Volume 78)
    - Business Letterbook 1909-1919 (Offsite-box AF-20, Volume 79)
    - Business Letterbook 1911-1917 (Offsite-box AF-20, Volume 80)
    - Business Letterbook 1912-1913 (Offsite-box AF-20, Volume 81)
    - Business Letterbook 1913-1915 (Offsite-box AF-28, Volume 82)
    - Business Letterbook 1913-1916 (Offsite-box AF-28, Volume 83)
    - Business Letterbook 1915-1916 (Offsite-box AF-28, Volume 84)
    - Business Letterbook 1915-1916 (Offsite-box AF-28, Volume 85)
    - Business Letterbook 1916-1917 (Offsite-box AF-29, Volume 86)
    - Business Letterbook and Telegraphs 1890-1892 (Offsite-box AF-31, Volume 87)
    - Business Letterbook and Telegraphs 1893-1901 (Offsite-box AF-29, Volume 88)
    - Business Letterbook and Telegraphs 1899-1911 (Offsite-box AF-29, Volume 89)
    - Business Letterbook and Telegraphs 1911-1912 (Offsite-box AF-29, Volume 90)
    - Personal Letterbook 1875-1902 (Offsite-box AF-31, Volume 91)
    - Personal Letterbook 1906-1911 (Offsite-box AF-28, Volume 92)
    - Personal Letterbook 1911-1914 (Offsite-box AF-28, Volume 93)
    - Personal Letterbook 1914-1917 (Offsite-box AF-29, Volume 94)
  - Subseries II.8: Abner Bartlett, 1890-1894
    - Business Letterbook 1890-1891 (Offsite-box AF-29, Volume 95)
    - Business Letterbook 1891-1894 (Offsite-box AF-29, Volume 96)
  - Subseries II.9: Margaret Astor Ward and Samuel Ward, 1848-1855
    - Personal Receipt Book, 1844-1858 (Offsite-box AF-28, Volume 97)
  - Subseries II.10: Susan Annette Gibbes, 1854-1872
    - Personal Receipt Book, 1857-1868 (Offsite-box AF-14, Volume 98)
    - Blotter, 1854-1872 (Offsite-box AF-14, Volume 99)
  - Subseries II.11: Edward Colegrove, 1893-1925
    - Estate Accounts, 1893-1925 (Offsite-box AF-31, Volume 100)
  - Subseries II.12: William Backhouse Astor Estate, 1876-1890
    - William Backhouse Astor's Estate belonging to William Waldorf Astor, 1876-1890 (Offsite-box AF-31, Volume 101)
  - Subseries II.13: Astor Homes, 1802
    - A survey of Astor home properties, 1802 (Offsite-box AF-28, Volume 102)